<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CameraKit</string>
    <string name="on_board_text">Order your accessories</string>
    <string name="on_board_text_2">Capture life\'s precious moments with precision and\n clarity, using our expert-approved camera accessories</string>
    <string name="login_text">Login to continue using this app</string>
    <string name="text1">I am an IT student at Imam Muhammad Bin Saud University. I have an interest in cybersecurity.
    </string>
    <string name="text2">I am an IT student at Imam Muhammad Bin Saud University. I have an interest in computer networking and network security</string>
    <string name="text3">I am Suha Alshahri, an Information Technology student at Imam Muhammad bin Saud Islamic University, passionate about technology and innovative solutions.</string>
    <string name="text4">I am an IT student at Imam Muhammad Bin Saud University. I have an interest in UI/UX</string>
    <string name="detail_text">-24.1 Megapixel CMOS sensor for exceptional image quality\n-Fast and accurate autofocus with 45 cross-type AF points\n-4K video recording at 30p and 1080p at 120p\n-Intuitive touchscreen LCD and ergonomic design\n-Builtin WiFi and Bluetooth for seamless connectivity\n-Compatible with Canon\'s range of EF and EFS lenses</string>
    <string name="home_text">Find the perfect gear for your camera with CameraKit. Browse and compare accessories, read reviews, and shop with exclusive discounts. Join our community of photographers and take your photography to the next level. Download now!\n\nCameraKit offers a comprehensive range of services to cater to the diverse needs of photographers. At its core, CameraKit provides an Accessory Finder feature, which allows users to search for compatible camera accessories based on their camera model. Additionally, the platform features Product Reviews, enabling users to read and write reviews of camera accessories, making informed purchasing decisions easier. CameraKit also integrates shopping capabilities, allowing users to purchase accessories directly through the app.</string>
</resources>